[Music]
Family is everything. Securing your
family's tomorrow and ensuring your
peace of mind is always our top
priority. Sometimes life gets busy and
essential details might slip your mind.
As your trusted insurance partner, we
are here to guide you through the
process of claiming any money that may
be payable to you but lying with us as a
pending amount. Let's understand why
this money which is payable to you is
pending with us.
Sometimes contact details change and we
are unable to reach you for any payment
due to you. In such cases your money
will remain pending with us. Always keep
your contact details like mobile number,
email ID and address updated with us.
Make sure your latest bank account
details are updated with us for smooth
processing of payments. When your
nominee is not aware of the policies
you've taken, it can lead to challenges
in reaching them. Always keep your
nominee informed about your insurance
policies and keep your nominee details
updated with us. for our NRI customers.
Providing complete NRE premium payment
proof that is the bank statements with
details of all the premiums paid is
crucial for processing payment to NRE
accounts. In case of pension policies,
choosing the annuity option post
maturity. If you don't do so, the money
will keep lying with us till you choose
the annuity option. But be rest assured,
your money is always safe with us. Now,
if you want to check if you have any
amount payable to you but lying pending
with us, we've made it convenient for
you. Visit our website at
www.iciprolife.com.
Click on the customer services tab and
go to the amount due to the
policyholders section. Enter the
required details like policy and band
number and click submit. A message on
your screen will guide you through the
following steps to claim your money.
Check the details on our mobile app. Go
to the service section. Select payout.
Go to the amount due to the policy
holders section. You can also visit our
nearest branch with your policy details
and bank account information. Our
customer service representative will
assist you. Alternatively, write to us
at lifeline at the rate iciprolife.com
or call our customer care number from
your registered mobile number.
We encourage you to always stay
connected to your policy and inform us
about any changes in your contact
details, bank account details, and
nominee details.
Act today and connect with us. We are
here caring for you at every step.